<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>truckinnutz on Bonehead Media</title>
    <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/categories/truckinnutz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in truckinnutz on Bonehead Media</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyleft © 2019, All original content on this site is Creative Commons 4.0 Non Commercial-Share alike.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 17:29:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://boneheadmedia.com/categories/truckinnutz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Huge Update</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/huge-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 17:29:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/huge-update/</guid>
      <description>This is huge. I mean super big huge!
So I am actually putting my money where my mouth is. I&amp;rsquo;ve been loathing the bull shit of Google, Facebook, Youtube and prettty much every large corporate giants out there that want to use its &amp;ldquo;users&amp;rdquo; as products to sell to their advertisers and shareholders. So I went and did it. But all in on this thing this time. I&amp;rsquo;ve embraced the &amp;ldquo;self hosting&amp;rdquo; concept and am running everything myself right down to the email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truckinnutz Is on Hiatus</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/truckinnutz-is-on-hiatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:13:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/truckinnutz-is-on-hiatus/</guid>
      <description>Another quick update is that I have put TruckinNutz on hiatus for a unknown amount of time. I have started a new podcast with the boys of Trucker Nation, USA called Break 19 Podcast. We have esentially merged the two together and have already recorded a couple of episodes. We intended it to be available as a videocast but I think we will end up just making it a good old fashioned audio podcast since the first couple of episodes have already turned out to be audio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 25 19 Pretrip Pt2 The Approach</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-25-19-pretrip-pt2-the-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:30:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-25-19-pretrip-pt2-the-approach/</guid>
      <description>As I said in the intro this is just how I do it. Some of you might do it differently but this is the way I was taught. I’ve seen a lot of old timers do it this as well. And it also kinda helps with the eld since you have to show 7-12 minutes doing a pre trip. Here is my steps as if I am on the road for the week already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 18 19 Quit Hating on Anchor</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-quit-hating-on-anchor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:30:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-quit-hating-on-anchor/</guid>
      <description>Why do people start a podcast? Some do it because its fun to talk. Others do it because there is subject that are passionate about and cant stop talking about it. But more and more I&amp;rsquo;m finding people starting podcasts with the intention of making money from that podcast. And I want to talk to you. Please, for the love of god. Stop! Podcasting started out as just people sharing on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 18 19 Pretrip Pt1</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-pretrip-pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:29:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-pretrip-pt1/</guid>
      <description>Let’s start with a question.
What is the most important thing on the truck? YOU!
Why?
Because you are important. Your family is depending on you. Your customers are depending on you. The general public is depending on you. You need to look at it as part of your job.
Can you safely operate that 40 ton truck?
Are you sick? Feel like throwing up? Don’t drive.
Are you tired?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 17 19 Dont Do This in Your Car</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-17-19-dont-do-this-in-your-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:28:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-17-19-dont-do-this-in-your-car/</guid>
      <description>Today I talk about 5 things people do in a car around big trucks that can end up with deadly consequences. And no thats not a click bait headline. These things are very important to know
 Dont pull in front of a truck only to make a left turn Dont Slow down to pass/speed up when being passed. Maintain your speed.
 Dont Pass only to slow down in front/pace truck from the front/”keep that driver from speeding”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 11 19 A Rough Week</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-11-19-a-rough-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:27:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-11-19-a-rough-week/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I was AWOL this week. I&amp;rsquo;ve had the flu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01-06-18 Safety on the Road</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-06-18-safety-on-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 14:18:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-06-18-safety-on-the-road/</guid>
      <description>You can now support me directly please visit https://anchor.fm/TruckinNutz/support
This episode was originally produced back in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01-04-19 All Brokers Lie</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-04-19-all-brokers-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 09:22:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-04-19-all-brokers-lie/</guid>
      <description>All Brokers Lie. It&amp;rsquo;s just a fact of our industry but drivers, even company drivers have got to stand up to them. Don&amp;rsquo;t let them just treat you like a second class citizen and work for free. You have the right to ask for detention pay. Talk with your companies dispatch! Also check out the Trucker Nation USA podcast. Another great podcast here on Anchor.fm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 28 Happy Friday</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-28-happy-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 09:17:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-28-happy-friday/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday went to hell, wife broke her arm, the podcast is distributed to more places and I gotta fricking work this weekend. All that and more on trays episode! You can email me at unklebonehead@pm.me. You can find me on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Minds.com etc. Do you have a question about truck driving and using the Anchor.fm app? Just send me a message right from the app and I am happy to answer anything!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardest Part About Trucking</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/hardest-part-about-trucking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 09:07:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/hardest-part-about-trucking/</guid>
      <description>Home time is the hardest. You get home and have to unwind. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to be socialable. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to talk with anybody. Then when you do unwind and are ready to be socialable it&amp;rsquo;s time to get back into trucking mode and the depression and anxiety of having to leave sets in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Important Device for a Driver</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/cb-importantance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:17:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/cb-importantance/</guid>
      <description>EPISODE NOTES So just a disclaimer if this is the first episode you’ve ever heard there is most likely a cuss word or two that gets thrown out once or twice. So I apologize in advance. But I do try to keep the show family friendly. This week I’m going to talk about a well documented and well proven piece of technology called the Citizens Band Radio. It can help you with your daily work better than any app on any phone operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 31 18 Trucker Lingo</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-trucker-lingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 17:24:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-trucker-lingo/</guid>
      <description>Trucking​ ​ Vocabulary Basically two​ ​types of trucks - Conventional​ ​- ​A ​truck​ ​with​ ​the​ engine​ ​mounted​ ​in​ ​front​ ​of​ ​ the​ ​cab. ​Has​ a ​nose - Cabover​ ​- ​A ​truck​ ​with​ the​ ​engine​ ​mounted​ ​between​ ​the​ frame​ rails​ ​and​ under​ the​ ​cab.
Manufacturers These​ are​ ​the​ class​ ​8 ​tractor/trailer​ ​makers. 1. Peterbuilt​ ​- Pete,​ Petercar 2. Freightliner​ - Freightshaker 3. Kenworth​ ​- ​Kwhopper 4. International​ ​- ​13​ ​letter​ ​shit​ spreader,​ ​corn​ ​binder 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 31 18 History of Trucking</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 17:19:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-history/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we get a special visit from Clifford the Big Red Truck.
I thank you all for the really quick acceptance of the podcast. 1 week and 35 downloads as of this posting! THANK YOU!
I give a really quick history lesson of the trucking industry.
You can email me questions or comments to unklebonehead2017@gmail.com
Subscribe to us on iTunes, Google Play Music, Stitcher, Tunein and Spreaker!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12-31-18 Clifford Takes Over</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-clifford-takes-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 16:57:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-clifford-takes-over/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we discover that Cliford has quite the sense of humor and has some semblance of emotions.
We also learn that his name stands for Certified Linux Intelligence For Organix Research and Development.
He is a 2nd generation A.I.known as an Organix organism from the year 2034.
Plus stats on the Freightliner Classic XL that he is embedded into.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>