<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NTROradio on Bonehead Media</title>
    <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/tags/ntroradio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NTROradio on Bonehead Media</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyleft © 2019, All original content on this site is Creative Commons 4.0 Non Commercial-Share alike.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:06:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://boneheadmedia.com/tags/ntroradio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NTROradio Is Cancelled-Maybe Not</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-is-cancelled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:06:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-is-cancelled/</guid>
      <description>Update as of 2019-10-5 I am currently researching how to get the stream back up for as cheap as possible. I will be returning the podcast soon and may well do some posts of artists as well. Keep and eye both here and NTROradio I have cancelled NTROradio. Both the podcast and the station. The station was run on Radionomy and since they ceased operations in the USA and forced everybody to move to paid versions of Shoutcast I am unable to afford it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 15</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 08:34:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-15/</guid>
      <description>Introducing K.C. the new host that replaces Zira. Music is entirely from CCMixter.
Shameless Site Promotion by Platinum Butterfly © copyright 2012 Licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution Noncommercial (3.0) license. http://dig.ccmixter.org/files/F_Fact/38008 Ft: Alex, Ms. Vybe
Speaking Power to Truth by Hans Atom © copyright 2013 Licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution Noncommercial (3.0) license. http://dig.ccmixter.org/files/hansatom/43773 Ft: Lonnie Ray Atkinson
(Let’s) Get UPPPPPPPPPPPPPPP! by CSoul © copyright 2012 Licensed under a Creative Commons Noncommercial Sampling Plus license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 14</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:00:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-14/</guid>
      <description>Band Name: Andy Michaels Album Name: Where are you Now Year Released: 2017 Website: www.andymichaelsmusic.com Music Style: Adult Contemporary Influences: Cold Play Sound Like: Maroon 5 Performing Rights Society: APRA (AUSTRALIA) Label Affiliation: Unsigned Geographic Hometown: Perth, Australia  Band Description: A singer/songwriter from Australia who has been compared with Live, James Blunt, The Script, Cat Stevens, and Neil Young , whilst his arrangements and music are also reminiscent of Cold Play, Maroon 5, Pink Floyd and Peter Gabriel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NTROradio 13</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:56:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-13/</guid>
      <description>Band Name: Henry Metal Album Name: War In Heaven Albun Released 2018 Website: www.henrymetal.net Music Style: Alt Rock / Metal Influences: Megadeth Sounds Like: Dio Performing Rights Society:None listed Label Affiliation: Unsigned Geographic Hometown: Chicago, USA  Band Description: Henry Metal is one of the most exciting new artists in rock and his new album, &amp;ldquo;War In Heaven,&amp;rdquo; was out everywhere January 1, 2018. Henry Metal debuted in late March of 2017 with the release of 2 singles, “Butthead Maven” and “Boss of Me,” both of which would appear on his first album “So It Hath Begun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 12</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:47:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-12/</guid>
      <description>***Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: When I first published this episode I had the intention of no longer podcasting about music. Well, I changed my mind. ***
Hi, You know me and you know how much I love indie music. I am going to have to say that this is the hardest podcast episode I’ve ever recorded. As much as I love introducing people to new music and the amazing artists that create it I am going to bring it all to an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NTROradio 11</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:46:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-11/</guid>
      <description>Murkocet is an American heavy metal band based out of Phoenix, Arizona. Formed in 2013, the band’s debut album ‘Digging Mercy’s Grave’ was released on January 14, 2017. The album consists of eleven tracks, two of which have been aired on Phoenix’s 98KUPD “Into The Pit” and another that was chosen by indie horror film director, Bob Clark of Reel Bloody Films to be the title track of his movie, ‘Strip Club Massacre’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 10</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-10/</guid>
      <description>Irish born Darragh J Brady is a rock steady musician and writer who is not afraid to go out on the edge if it means bringing something good back from it.
Dar.Ra has graced the UK national charts and dance charts with two top 40’s and two number one dance records with acts signed to EMI, BMG, Festival Records (Australia) plus remixed legends like Frankie Goes to Hollywood, Tears 4 Fears, Urban Harmonix ft Rachel Brown (Faithless, Groove Armada) and many others along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 09</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-09/</guid>
      <description>All Chile Colorado</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 08</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-08/</guid>
      <description>All Dizzy Box Nine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 07</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-07/</guid>
      <description>Featuring Terminal Degree! Awesome metal played on Cello and Electric Violins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 06</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-06/</guid>
      <description>Featuring Wally Maggs, Charissa and King George</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 05</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:20:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-05/</guid>
      <description>Hence the Noise - Minute with Me - My Demise Cody Joe Hodges
- Roll That Way</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 04</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:59:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-04/</guid>
      <description>This weeks artists Hosted by Rich
Xavier Boscher 1. Metronome Celeste 2. Quinachridone
Mightier Than Me 1. To Be Determined 2. Get Gone
Rewind Segment Hosted by Zira
Black Dawn 1. I Could Never Be 2. I Want To Fly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 03</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:59:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-03/</guid>
      <description>Unkle Bonehead Couldnt make it this episode so Zira filled in for him.
The C. R. Ecker Band – Duty, Honor, Country and Good Ol’ Days
Ronnie Clinton – Southern Pride
Plus a new segment called NTROradio Rewind. Songs from our vault.
Carolina Morn – America Stands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 02</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:59:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-02/</guid>
      <description>Featuring:
Christopher Hawley - 9 Tattoos
Braintenna - Crown
Voice of Addiction – Corporate Pariah
A DOUBLE SHOT! Fractured Spine 1. Have Earned My Despair 2. Still Beating
For some awesome interviews with Indie artists I suggest you check out the podcast Backstage at Nadeau media</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 01</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 04:00:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-01/</guid>
      <description>DOUBLE SHOT!! Mike Thompson Little Dreamer Thunder Island feat. Collin Raye
Vovkulaka Defy
For some awesome interviews with Indie artists I suggest you check out the podcast Backstage at Nadeau media</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>