<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bonehead Media</title>
    <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bonehead Media</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyleft © 2019, All original content on this site is Creative Commons 4.0 Non Commercial-Share alike.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 11:06:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://boneheadmedia.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ipfs Enabled</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/ipfs-enabled/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 11:06:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/ipfs-enabled/</guid>
      <description>In episode 21 of The Self Hosted Podcast I talked about IPFS. Well if you are reading this then I did it. This website is now on IPFS and you if I did it right it looks no different than the regular website. Which I hope I got it right because that would be so cool. But I still dont like that whatever you put on IPFS it&amp;rsquo;s online forever. So you better be sure you stand behind what you say and dont change your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Am Not Slacking</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/i-am-not-slacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 18:30:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/i-am-not-slacking/</guid>
      <description>**I can assure you I am not slacking. I will be recordng a new episode this weekend while streaming on both Dlive and a test station I have been setting up for NTROradio. I would share the link for NTROradio with all of you but it&amp;rsquo;s far from being ready for more than a few select people I trust to listen directly to my personal server. Lets just say that I have a friend with a lot of experience playing around with Azuracast and he is putting it through some tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep21 Azuracast, IPFS and Data Detox Kit</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 10:54:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep21/</guid>
      <description>Its a new year and now is the perfect time for you to make the commitment to protecting yourself, your privacy and your data. How? By self hosting of course! Self hosted radio station, websites and files and detoxing your data all right here, right now on The Self Hosted Podcast!
Banter Over the last 20 episodes I&amp;rsquo;ve focussed primarily on apps that can be installed and used through Yunohost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP Ep20.5 Merry Christmas from Bonehead Media</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 09:48:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20-5/</guid>
      <description>Download MP3 here
You can watch LIVE me on DLive! This is not a normal episode!
This is a replay of my last Christmas show. It originaly aired both in the feed for The Unkle Bonehead Show and on UBSN.net. My first radio station that was all me. In it you will here me reference. Linux for the rest of us training videos. They are still available but pretty dated since this was recorded 2011-12-24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP-Ep20 Changing My Mind, Again!</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 05:29:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20/</guid>
      <description>Download MP3 file
Preroll I&amp;rsquo;m tring something new, Pixelfed is in the news and a whole lot more coming up in number 20 of The Self Hosted Podcast!
Housekeeping and Support Support Framasoft- They are looking to bring live streaming to PeerTube!
Tool Tip VSCodium
News Fediverse Pixelfed awarded grant from NLnet
Russian Police Raid NGINX
Zepplin Ransomware targets Tech and Health Co
Snatch ransomware reboots windows in safe mode to bypass antivirus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NTRO radio is back and better than ever!</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/ntroradioisback/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 18:59:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/ntroradioisback/</guid>
      <description>This post was updated on 2019-12-08
So NTROradio has been reborn! It is now a Funkwhale instance running on my new Yunohost server in my home. I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you more about it in this weeks podcast but just suffice it to say the hard drive died and I swapped it out with a new one.
Above you shoule be seeing an empeded player from NTROradio with my demo cover of Bat Out of Hell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP Ep19 Funkwhale - Putting the Pod back into Podcasting</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 07:10:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep19/</guid>
      <description>Download Here
Music provided by Unfa
Internet Archive could use your support! &amp;gt;I ask only once a year: please help the Internet Archive today. Right now, we have a 2-to-1 Matching Gift Campaign, so you can triple your impact! Most can’t afford to give, but we hope you can. The average donation is $45. If everyone reading this chips in just $5, we can end this fundraiser today. All we need is the price of a paperback book to sustain a non-profit website the whole world depends on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep18 LollipopCloud and Funkwhale Podcasters Group</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 20:52:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep18/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
Email me at unklebonehead@nixnet.email **This episode is brought to you by LollipopCloud
Housekeeping  @Naschbarschaft on Mastodon alerted me to mp3 enclosures were not in the rss feed for Bonehead Media.com Thank you I am learning how to put them into the rss templates in hugo. I will get this fixed.
 I didnt get to go home again so I&amp;rsquo;m in the truck again recording this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Update 2019-11-17</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/quick-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 11:54:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/quick-update/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow just Bonehead Media on activitypub Just search in your favorite activitypub app ie Mastodon, Hubzilla, etc for @BoneheadMedia@bots.tinysubversions.com And you should be able to subscribe to this website&amp;rsquo;s rss though activitypub. I used the Feed Converter by Darius Kazemi. It&amp;rsquo;s a free service that he hosts and I hope to implement it on my own for others as he does once I get a VPS set up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP-Ep-17 Epic News</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 19:02:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep17/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
This episode is brought to you by NixNet where freedom is served with a slice of liberty.
Pre Roll Recording on the run, a whole bunch of super exciting news in the Fediverse and a whole lot more coming up on episode 17 of The Self Hosted Podcast!
Banter  This episode will be out the week of November 17th. By the end of this week this podcast will have well over 1000 downloads on Anchor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep16 LimeSurvey and being dealt a shitty day</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 13:04:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep16/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
Big update since the recording! new contact email is unklebonehead@nixnet.email
News Massive exodus of India&amp;rsquo;s Twitter moved to Mastodon - This is a bull shit quote from the article. &amp;gt;While many have hailed Mastodon as a great alternative to Twitter, some have pointed out that its not as easy to use, which means its unlikely that Mastodon is going to take over - even in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP-Ep15 This is some scary s**t</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 06:38:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep15/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
News Links Yunohost 3.7 Testing asking for feedback
 We just released a new testing version for YunoHost and would be happy to receive feedback before releasing it as a stable version :yum:
This release includes quite important changes in YunoHost’s internal, and therefore requires careful validation to minimize the amount of remaining bugs.
 Major changes are: - Group and permission mechanism
 Improvements to detect app installs that broke critical parts of the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep14 Pubcast, WriteFreely and Plume</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 14:19:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep14/</guid>
      <description>Download Here
Music provided by Unfa
Follow me across the fediverse! unklebonehead@hzhome.ntroradio.com
So I got started on FreeCodeCamp As I mentioned in a blog post last week I want to learn how to code. Mainly so I can understand the topics I am covering here on this podcast and to help me be a better self hoster but I would love to get a new job where I am home a lot more than just 34 hrs a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I want learn how to Code</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/learning-to-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 09:00:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/learning-to-code/</guid>
      <description>Cool, wait, You? Yes me. I&amp;rsquo;m actually feeling a &amp;ldquo;want to know how&amp;rdquo;. That&amp;rsquo;s really the only way I know how to express it. As some of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve used linux for a vey long time. Since mid 2010 I&amp;rsquo;ve been running some form of Linux as a daily driver and it&amp;rsquo;s been mostly Ubuntu/Debian flavors with the exception of the two weeks I tried to install Arch the &amp;ldquo;Arch way&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP Ep13</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 07:14:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep13/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
PreRoll Advert - This episode is brought to you by The Fediverse. The Fediverse is a collection of nearly 40 decentralized apps that can connect with each other. You can join or even host an instance yourself on your own server. More than just social networks they cover just about everything from blogging to cloud storage. PeerTube, Plume, FunkWhale Visit Fediverse Party to learn more today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Podcasts Without the Fluff</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/great-podcasts-without-the-fluff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 09:31:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/great-podcasts-without-the-fluff/</guid>
      <description>So I did some thinking about my last post After chewing on that last post for a couple of days I thought I should mention some good podcasts that done have the crap of the fluff taking up 50% of thier episodes. Now let me just say that these are not free from advertising. But the adverts in them are done tastefully and dont take up half the show. And they will actually respond to an email from someone who isnt a patron on patreon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I start another podcast?</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/considering-a-new-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 07:30:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/considering-a-new-podcast/</guid>
      <description>I have to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m actually considering it You may have figured out by now that when I find something new the first thing I do is look for a podcast about it. I know I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one in the world that does this. But this time I&amp;rsquo;m not so sure about starting it. I want to do it but I dont want to, lol. I&amp;rsquo;m so indecisive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking the Plunge on Full</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/taking-the-plunge-on-full/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 14:14:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/taking-the-plunge-on-full/</guid>
      <description>Hubzilla hour 36 update Well it&amp;rsquo;s been just over 36 hrs I&amp;rsquo;ve been on Hubzilla and I really do still like it. Wait, I love it! I like it so much that I am considering take the full on plunge and going in up to my neck in it. I want to get into exeriencing the full effect with the webpages app and build a site out of it. Just to see what I can do with my measley coding skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHV-Ep7 TSHP Cross Post Hubzilla</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshp-cross-post-hubzilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 13:22:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshp-cross-post-hubzilla/</guid>
      <description>As promised yesterday I said I would post this today. Well here it is. I recorded this episode while recording TSHP Ep12. I did this so you can actually see with your own eyes Hubzilla. In my own humble and honest opinion it is probably the most powerful app on the fediverse. - It can interact with Ostatus, ActivityPup, Freindica, diaspora and just about anything out there.
 It has apps out the wazoo for you to do anything with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Updates</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 21:11:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/some-updates/</guid>
      <description>In case you hadn&amp;rsquo;t noticed I&amp;rsquo;ve been a bit busy here recently. Not only has the entire site been redone but it&amp;rsquo;s still not complete. While it is complete enough to get going with new content. Here is what I&amp;rsquo;ve done. - Now made with Hugo! I went back to Hugo because I like the simplicity of it and how I can make changes right on my laptop during the week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep12 Hubzilla and More News</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep12-hubzilla-and-more-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 04:44:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep12-hubzilla-and-more-news/</guid>
      <description>Download untracked Mp3 here
There is a video that I recorded for this to show Hubzilla. I will post it tomarrow in it&amp;rsquo;s own post.
Preroll Quick bit of news and then we play with Hubzilla. Right here on episode 12 of The Self Hosted Podcast!
Housekeeping Yunohost has been upgraded to 3.6.5.2 along with Yunohost Admin panel. It is now at 3.6.5. Nextcloud-ynh has also been updated to 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep11 News and Updates</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep11-news-and-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep11-news-and-updates/</guid>
      <description>Download untracked Mp3 here
I&amp;rsquo;m back! Now with a redneck, tricked out Frankenputer latop. But its powered by KDENeon and backedup by Yunohost. It&amp;rsquo;s episode 11 and I got some news, opinions and updates for you right here, right now on The Self Hosted Podcast.
Housekeeping My laptop broke. Thats why I&amp;rsquo;ve been silent. But I was able to jerry rig it enough that its usable. I&amp;rsquo;ll post pics or you can go see them on Mastodon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Unkle Bonehead</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Who? Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Unkle Bonehead aka Ryan Ridenour, I&amp;rsquo;m a 49 yr old truck driver by trade and have just over 27 years in the industry with over 2.5 million accident free miles. I create podcasts and other digital media. I am also an amateur self hoster, a Fediverse Evangelist and fanboy of the Yunohost server distribution based on Debian.
Digital audio I originally got into podcasting purely by accident while researching how to record my own music on the computer back in 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact &amp; Subscribe to the Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Socialize with me Starting 2019-12-15 you can watch me record every episode every weekend LIVE on Dlive! I will also be streaming live periodicaly through out the week! You can follow the rss of Bonehead Media site through ActivityPub by using @BoneheadMedia@bots.tinysubversions.com - this is not a feed I can respond to, but for you to catch the feed updates on social media that use ActivityPub ie Mastodon.
Mastodon | Pixelfed | Email Me | Hubzilla - I will get this back up when I get a vps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Important Links</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/links/</guid>
      <description>The site that was instrumental in getting me started with self hosting and taking control of my data. Was down for a short time but is now back online with several maintainers. This site is where I found Yunohost and all the tools I needed to kick the big tech companies out of my life forever.
NixNet - Freedom served with a slice of Liberty
Switching Software - formerly known as Switching Social</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Us</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/support/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to support me you can find the links at the bottom of the site. But I would rather you support someone on this growing list below. They can use your help way more than I need it. Just you taking the time out of your day to listen and visit my site helps me more than you know.
Ella K.,Cyberpunk Goddess @ella_kane@hackers.town aka Eloisa &amp;amp; them Seagulls @eloisa@masto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep10 Communication on Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-08-ep10-communitcation-on-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-08-ep10-communitcation-on-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
Pre-roll The last couple of weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve seen on these message signs over the highways the phrase &amp;ldquo;Turn signals-the original instant message&amp;rdquo;. And the talk on the CB radio was hilarious as you can imagine. But the one thing all of us truck drivers agree on is that the turn signal is not the original instant messsage. It&amp;rsquo;s the middle finger. And speaking of instant messenges this is Ep10:Communication on Yunohost right here, right now on The Self Hosted Podcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep9Getting Help with Your Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-01-ep9-getting-help-with-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-01-ep9-getting-help-with-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Ep 9  Download Mp3 Download two songs from me for free! CC4.0! Play them in your podcast if you have one! Hammer On Down Work It Out
Pre Roll I was at a TA truckstop earlier this week. And they had a Verizon kiosk inside and there was actually a Verizon employee there. I may have jokingly asked him if he had any phones that didnt have ios or android on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I record my Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep5/</guid>
      <description>To be honest, this should be a &amp;ldquo;Dont drink and vidcast&amp;rdquo; video. I may or may not have had a couple of beers before recording this. This how I record all of my podcasts, whether I&amp;rsquo;m at home in the studio or on the road in the truck. The process and apps are all the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I am currently using on my Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep6/</guid>
      <description>Just me showing you what I am currently using on my own home server. Airsonic Grav Flat File CMS Searx Roundcube Nextcloud PeerTube TTRss</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep8 Commit2Quit</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-25-ep8-commit2quit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-25-ep8-commit2quit/</guid>
      <description>Ep8 Commit2Quit  Download Here
Housekeeping It seems that this podcasts goal has already been achieved. It has inspired 2 people to start self hosting. I got a couple of notifications on Mastodon that one is researching on how to self host on bsd and the other actually installed Yunohost! Thats frickin AWESOME! CONGRATS TO BOTH OF YOU! And I sincerely hope it works out for each your situations. Especially the one doing it on bsd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep7 Securering Your Yunohost Server</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-18-ep7-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-18-ep7-security/</guid>
      <description>Ep7 Security  Download Mp3
Housekeeping I just recorded episode 4 of The Self Hosted Vidcast. I uninstalled Wordpress and showed how to install a static html site on Yunohost. Bonehead Media is back to being a simple static html site. It&amp;rsquo;s only got 2 pages that I built in Bootstrap Studio. I&amp;rsquo;ll flesh it out more in the future. I would like to turn it into a theme for Pelican or Hugo and post the shownotes to the front page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to remove Wordpress from Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep4/</guid>
      <description>This is how you uninstall Wordpress and install a static html site to Yunohost. Get Yunohost - https://yunohost.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep6 How to Take Back Control</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-12-ep6-how/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-12-ep6-how/</guid>
      <description>Ep6 How to take back control  Download Here
How to take back control https://switching.social/guide-to-switching/
First we need to look at what we need to replace to rid our lives of these companies. 1. Communication/Email/Chat/Conferancing 2. Office/Doc/Colaboration 3. File storage/Sharing 4. News 5. Social Networking 6. Education 7. Entertainment
To truly get rid of Google you will need to replace your Android phone! More on this towards the end. These can all be covered using some ethical and free companies such as Framasoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep5 Getting Back Control</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-11-ep5-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-11-ep5-control/</guid>
      <description>Ep5 Getting Back Control  Download Here
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be totally honest with you. I didnt really think the course of this podcast through before starting it. I got excited when I found out about Yunohost and went totally ADD thinking that people have to know about this distro! I just hit record and started talking without thinking. I didnt put any kind of structure into it or really any kind of planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Wordpress on Yunohst</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep3/</guid>
      <description>Look how easy it is to install Wordpress on Yunohost! It only actually took minutes and minimal attention from me. But because I cant never shut up it made a 30 minute video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep4 The Internet Cube</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-04-ep4-the-internet-cube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-04-ep4-the-internet-cube/</guid>
      <description>Ep4 The Internet Cube  Download Mp3 #### Rethinking the direction of the podcast I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing some major thinking about the direction of where I want to take this podcast. I was listening to one of the episodes as I usually do. Us podcasters do that alot. Listen to ourselves in order to critique our abililites. We&amp;rsquo;re not really that self important, we are are our worst and toughest critics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep3 Why You Should Know DNS</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep3-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep3-dns/</guid>
      <description>Ep3 Why You Should Know DNS  Download Mp3 I love the artwork for this episode! And I just had to use it when I saw it. It was created by @aleks@cybre.space. I&amp;rsquo;ve also ran across a couple of memes that I cant stop laughing at. I&amp;rsquo;ll be using those in future episodes as well. The cat is out of the bag and people are discovering the podcast. So if you are new, well I guess at this point everybody is new, lol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep2 Choosing Yunohost and The Fediverse</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep2-choosing-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep2-choosing-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Ep2 Choosing Yunohost and The Fediverse 
Download Episode #### What it is If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever messed with Linux you have undoubtedly experienced the dreaded (but fun) thing called &amp;ldquo;distro hopping&amp;rdquo;. Where you constantly download and install tons of different distros and use them to see what they are like and how well they run. Hell you may be running 3-4 of them on a pc at any given time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep1 Six Questions</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep1-six-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep1-six-questions/</guid>
      <description>Ep1 Six Questions 
Download Mp3 Who, what, where, when, why and how.
Who am I? Greetings! If this is the first time you&amp;rsquo;ve ever ran across me I am Unkle Bonehead and welcome to the Self Hosted Podcast, a journey into taking control of your data and entering the Fediverse. It&amp;rsquo;s not only my journey but it just might be yours as well.
Why? Because large corporations such as Google, Facebook, Twitter, Amazon, etc have your data in their control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yunohst Post Intall</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep2/</guid>
      <description>The step called &amp;ldquo;post-installation&amp;rdquo; is actually the initial configuration of YunoHost. It has to be done just after the installation of the system itself. You can do it from through ssh, directly on the server or through a web browser. The browser is what I did because it is the easiest for people like me. Who dont know what they are doing.
Post-Installation The step called &amp;ldquo;post-installation&amp;rdquo; is actually the initial configuration of YunoHost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep1/</guid>
      <description>Talking about and installing Yunohost. I used virtualbox instead of an actual machine but the process is the same. Step1 - Make coffee Step2 - Download the correct iso for your machine Step3 - Install</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now With Less Google</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/now-with-less-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 07:45:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/now-with-less-google/</guid>
      <description>Hopefully by the end of the week I will be 100% Google free. The only exception is on my phone. I am no longer using gmail except for a couple of login that I need to change and am working on porting all my emails over to my new email. Im also switching to the News app on Nextcloud for my rss reader and am deciding on whether or not I want to use Nextclouds Music app for my music library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huge Update</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/huge-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 17:29:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/huge-update/</guid>
      <description>This is huge. I mean super big huge!
So I am actually putting my money where my mouth is. I&amp;rsquo;ve been loathing the bull shit of Google, Facebook, Youtube and prettty much every large corporate giants out there that want to use its &amp;ldquo;users&amp;rdquo; as products to sell to their advertisers and shareholders. So I went and did it. But all in on this thing this time. I&amp;rsquo;ve embraced the &amp;ldquo;self hosting&amp;rdquo; concept and am running everything myself right down to the email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pound for Pound</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/break19/pound-for-pound/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:29:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/break19/pound-for-pound/</guid>
      <description>Audio only player at bottom of post
   Another audio only episode. But I did throw in some extra footage I shot a couple years ago while driving Clifford for the Youtube viewers. Plus this episode was greatly improved. Now contains MORE WOLFIE!
You can find us on Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts and Spotify as well as where ever free podcasts are sold!
Email us at break19podcast@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Break19 Podcast Anybody Got a Copy</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/break19/break19-podcast-anybody-got-a-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:29:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/break19/break19-podcast-anybody-got-a-copy/</guid>
      <description>Audio only player at bottom of post
  Man sues parents for getting rid of huge porno collection. Mrs Bonehead submitted this.
www.wthr.com/article/man-sues-parents-getting-rid-his-vast-porn-collection-1
Social media users flocked to Pornhub during major Facebook, Instagram outages www.theblaze.com/news/pornhub-traffic-surce-during-facebook-outage
71% of Drivers Take Photos of Roadway Emergencies www.automotive-fleet.com/328847/71-of-drivers-take-photos-of-roadway-emergencies
Phone Addicts Worse Threat Than Drunk Drivers, Study Finds www.automotive-fleet.com/329295/phone-addicts-worse-threat-than-drunk-drivers-study-finds
Driver Awarded $80 Million
www.truckersnews.com/driver-award-80m-in-false-log-accident-suit/
DOT&amp;rsquo;s hours of service proposal listed for early June publication</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truckinnutz Is on Hiatus</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/truckinnutz-is-on-hiatus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:13:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/truckinnutz-is-on-hiatus/</guid>
      <description>Another quick update is that I have put TruckinNutz on hiatus for a unknown amount of time. I have started a new podcast with the boys of Trucker Nation, USA called Break 19 Podcast. We have esentially merged the two together and have already recorded a couple of episodes. We intended it to be available as a videocast but I think we will end up just making it a good old fashioned audio podcast since the first couple of episodes have already turned out to be audio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NTROradio Is Cancelled-Maybe Not</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-is-cancelled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 16:06:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-is-cancelled/</guid>
      <description>Update as of 2019-10-5 I am currently researching how to get the stream back up for as cheap as possible. I will be returning the podcast soon and may well do some posts of artists as well. Keep and eye both here and NTROradio I have cancelled NTROradio. Both the podcast and the station. The station was run on Radionomy and since they ceased operations in the USA and forced everybody to move to paid versions of Shoutcast I am unable to afford it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 25 19 Pretrip Pt2 The Approach</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-25-19-pretrip-pt2-the-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:30:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-25-19-pretrip-pt2-the-approach/</guid>
      <description>As I said in the intro this is just how I do it. Some of you might do it differently but this is the way I was taught. I’ve seen a lot of old timers do it this as well. And it also kinda helps with the eld since you have to show 7-12 minutes doing a pre trip. Here is my steps as if I am on the road for the week already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 18 19 Quit Hating on Anchor</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-quit-hating-on-anchor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:30:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-quit-hating-on-anchor/</guid>
      <description>Why do people start a podcast? Some do it because its fun to talk. Others do it because there is subject that are passionate about and cant stop talking about it. But more and more I&amp;rsquo;m finding people starting podcasts with the intention of making money from that podcast. And I want to talk to you. Please, for the love of god. Stop! Podcasting started out as just people sharing on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 18 19 Pretrip Pt1</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-pretrip-pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:29:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-18-19-pretrip-pt1/</guid>
      <description>Let’s start with a question.
What is the most important thing on the truck? YOU!
Why?
Because you are important. Your family is depending on you. Your customers are depending on you. The general public is depending on you. You need to look at it as part of your job.
Can you safely operate that 40 ton truck?
Are you sick? Feel like throwing up? Don’t drive.
Are you tired?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 17 19 Dont Do This in Your Car</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-17-19-dont-do-this-in-your-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:28:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-17-19-dont-do-this-in-your-car/</guid>
      <description>Today I talk about 5 things people do in a car around big trucks that can end up with deadly consequences. And no thats not a click bait headline. These things are very important to know
 Dont pull in front of a truck only to make a left turn Dont Slow down to pass/speed up when being passed. Maintain your speed.
 Dont Pass only to slow down in front/pace truck from the front/”keep that driver from speeding”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 11 19 A Rough Week</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-11-19-a-rough-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 10:27:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-11-19-a-rough-week/</guid>
      <description>Sorry I was AWOL this week. I&amp;rsquo;ve had the flu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01-06-18 Safety on the Road</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-06-18-safety-on-the-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 14:18:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-06-18-safety-on-the-road/</guid>
      <description>You can now support me directly please visit https://anchor.fm/TruckinNutz/support
This episode was originally produced back in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01-04-19 All Brokers Lie</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-04-19-all-brokers-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 09:22:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/01-04-19-all-brokers-lie/</guid>
      <description>All Brokers Lie. It&amp;rsquo;s just a fact of our industry but drivers, even company drivers have got to stand up to them. Don&amp;rsquo;t let them just treat you like a second class citizen and work for free. You have the right to ask for detention pay. Talk with your companies dispatch! Also check out the Trucker Nation USA podcast. Another great podcast here on Anchor.fm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12-30-18Sunday Morning Coffee</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-30-sunday-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 09:20:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-30-sunday-morning/</guid>
      <description>A quick review of Netfix&amp;rsquo;s Bird Box, my opinion on the stupid argument of the &amp;ldquo;Legends of Podcasting&amp;rdquo; bad mouthing Anchor. How They have based to their argument from a false perspective and the future of TruckinNutz and my other podcast Driving Common Sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 28 Happy Friday</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-28-happy-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 09:17:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-28-happy-friday/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday went to hell, wife broke her arm, the podcast is distributed to more places and I gotta fricking work this weekend. All that and more on trays episode! You can email me at unklebonehead@pm.me. You can find me on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Minds.com etc. Do you have a question about truck driving and using the Anchor.fm app? Just send me a message right from the app and I am happy to answer anything!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardest Part About Trucking</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/hardest-part-about-trucking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 09:07:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/hardest-part-about-trucking/</guid>
      <description>Home time is the hardest. You get home and have to unwind. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to be socialable. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to talk with anybody. Then when you do unwind and are ready to be socialable it&amp;rsquo;s time to get back into trucking mode and the depression and anxiety of having to leave sets in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 15</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 08:34:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-15/</guid>
      <description>Introducing K.C. the new host that replaces Zira. Music is entirely from CCMixter.
Shameless Site Promotion by Platinum Butterfly © copyright 2012 Licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution Noncommercial (3.0) license. http://dig.ccmixter.org/files/F_Fact/38008 Ft: Alex, Ms. Vybe
Speaking Power to Truth by Hans Atom © copyright 2013 Licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution Noncommercial (3.0) license. http://dig.ccmixter.org/files/hansatom/43773 Ft: Lonnie Ray Atkinson
(Let’s) Get UPPPPPPPPPPPPPPP! by CSoul © copyright 2012 Licensed under a Creative Commons Noncommercial Sampling Plus license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Important Device for a Driver</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/cb-importantance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 16:17:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/cb-importantance/</guid>
      <description>EPISODE NOTES So just a disclaimer if this is the first episode you’ve ever heard there is most likely a cuss word or two that gets thrown out once or twice. So I apologize in advance. But I do try to keep the show family friendly. This week I’m going to talk about a well documented and well proven piece of technology called the Citizens Band Radio. It can help you with your daily work better than any app on any phone operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 31 18 Trucker Lingo</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-trucker-lingo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 17:24:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-trucker-lingo/</guid>
      <description>Trucking​ ​ Vocabulary Basically two​ ​types of trucks - Conventional​ ​- ​A ​truck​ ​with​ ​the​ engine​ ​mounted​ ​in​ ​front​ ​of​ ​ the​ ​cab. ​Has​ a ​nose - Cabover​ ​- ​A ​truck​ ​with​ the​ ​engine​ ​mounted​ ​between​ ​the​ frame​ rails​ ​and​ under​ the​ ​cab.
Manufacturers These​ are​ ​the​ class​ ​8 ​tractor/trailer​ ​makers. 1. Peterbuilt​ ​- Pete,​ Petercar 2. Freightliner​ - Freightshaker 3. Kenworth​ ​- ​Kwhopper 4. International​ ​- ​13​ ​letter​ ​shit​ spreader,​ ​corn​ ​binder 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 31 18 History of Trucking</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 17:19:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-history/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we get a special visit from Clifford the Big Red Truck.
I thank you all for the really quick acceptance of the podcast. 1 week and 35 downloads as of this posting! THANK YOU!
I give a really quick history lesson of the trucking industry.
You can email me questions or comments to unklebonehead2017@gmail.com
Subscribe to us on iTunes, Google Play Music, Stitcher, Tunein and Spreaker!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12-31-18 Clifford Takes Over</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-clifford-takes-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 16:57:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/12-31-18-clifford-takes-over/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we discover that Cliford has quite the sense of humor and has some semblance of emotions.
We also learn that his name stands for Certified Linux Intelligence For Organix Research and Development.
He is a 2nd generation A.I.known as an Organix organism from the year 2034.
Plus stats on the Freightliner Classic XL that he is embedded into.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 14</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 07:00:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-14/</guid>
      <description>Band Name: Andy Michaels Album Name: Where are you Now Year Released: 2017 Website: www.andymichaelsmusic.com Music Style: Adult Contemporary Influences: Cold Play Sound Like: Maroon 5 Performing Rights Society: APRA (AUSTRALIA) Label Affiliation: Unsigned Geographic Hometown: Perth, Australia  Band Description: A singer/songwriter from Australia who has been compared with Live, James Blunt, The Script, Cat Stevens, and Neil Young , whilst his arrangements and music are also reminiscent of Cold Play, Maroon 5, Pink Floyd and Peter Gabriel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NTROradio 13</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:56:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-13/</guid>
      <description>Band Name: Henry Metal Album Name: War In Heaven Albun Released 2018 Website: www.henrymetal.net Music Style: Alt Rock / Metal Influences: Megadeth Sounds Like: Dio Performing Rights Society:None listed Label Affiliation: Unsigned Geographic Hometown: Chicago, USA  Band Description: Henry Metal is one of the most exciting new artists in rock and his new album, &amp;ldquo;War In Heaven,&amp;rdquo; was out everywhere January 1, 2018. Henry Metal debuted in late March of 2017 with the release of 2 singles, “Butthead Maven” and “Boss of Me,” both of which would appear on his first album “So It Hath Begun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 12</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:47:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-12/</guid>
      <description>***Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: When I first published this episode I had the intention of no longer podcasting about music. Well, I changed my mind. ***
Hi, You know me and you know how much I love indie music. I am going to have to say that this is the hardest podcast episode I’ve ever recorded. As much as I love introducing people to new music and the amazing artists that create it I am going to bring it all to an end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NTROradio 11</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:46:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-11/</guid>
      <description>Murkocet is an American heavy metal band based out of Phoenix, Arizona. Formed in 2013, the band’s debut album ‘Digging Mercy’s Grave’ was released on January 14, 2017. The album consists of eleven tracks, two of which have been aired on Phoenix’s 98KUPD “Into The Pit” and another that was chosen by indie horror film director, Bob Clark of Reel Bloody Films to be the title track of his movie, ‘Strip Club Massacre’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 10</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-10/</guid>
      <description>Irish born Darragh J Brady is a rock steady musician and writer who is not afraid to go out on the edge if it means bringing something good back from it.
Dar.Ra has graced the UK national charts and dance charts with two top 40’s and two number one dance records with acts signed to EMI, BMG, Festival Records (Australia) plus remixed legends like Frankie Goes to Hollywood, Tears 4 Fears, Urban Harmonix ft Rachel Brown (Faithless, Groove Armada) and many others along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 09</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-09/</guid>
      <description>All Chile Colorado</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 08</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-08/</guid>
      <description>All Dizzy Box Nine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 07</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-07/</guid>
      <description>Featuring Terminal Degree! Awesome metal played on Cello and Electric Violins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 06</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:25:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-06/</guid>
      <description>Featuring Wally Maggs, Charissa and King George</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 05</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 06:20:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-05/</guid>
      <description>Hence the Noise - Minute with Me - My Demise Cody Joe Hodges
- Roll That Way</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 04</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:59:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-04/</guid>
      <description>This weeks artists Hosted by Rich
Xavier Boscher 1. Metronome Celeste 2. Quinachridone
Mightier Than Me 1. To Be Determined 2. Get Gone
Rewind Segment Hosted by Zira
Black Dawn 1. I Could Never Be 2. I Want To Fly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 03</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:59:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-03/</guid>
      <description>Unkle Bonehead Couldnt make it this episode so Zira filled in for him.
The C. R. Ecker Band – Duty, Honor, Country and Good Ol’ Days
Ronnie Clinton – Southern Pride
Plus a new segment called NTROradio Rewind. Songs from our vault.
Carolina Morn – America Stands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 02</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:59:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-02/</guid>
      <description>Featuring:
Christopher Hawley - 9 Tattoos
Braintenna - Crown
Voice of Addiction – Corporate Pariah
A DOUBLE SHOT! Fractured Spine 1. Have Earned My Despair 2. Still Beating
For some awesome interviews with Indie artists I suggest you check out the podcast Backstage at Nadeau media</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ntroradio 01</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 04:00:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/ntroradio/ntroradio-01/</guid>
      <description>DOUBLE SHOT!! Mike Thompson Little Dreamer Thunder Island feat. Collin Raye
Vovkulaka Defy
For some awesome interviews with Indie artists I suggest you check out the podcast Backstage at Nadeau media</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>