<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tshp on Bonehead Media</title>
    <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/categories/tshp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tshp on Bonehead Media</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyleft © 2019, All original content on this site is Creative Commons 4.0 Non Commercial-Share alike.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 10:54:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://boneheadmedia.com/categories/tshp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep21 Azuracast, IPFS and Data Detox Kit</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 10:54:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep21/</guid>
      <description>Its a new year and now is the perfect time for you to make the commitment to protecting yourself, your privacy and your data. How? By self hosting of course! Self hosted radio station, websites and files and detoxing your data all right here, right now on The Self Hosted Podcast!
Banter Over the last 20 episodes I&amp;rsquo;ve focussed primarily on apps that can be installed and used through Yunohost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP Ep20.5 Merry Christmas from Bonehead Media</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 09:48:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20-5/</guid>
      <description>Download MP3 here
You can watch LIVE me on DLive! This is not a normal episode!
This is a replay of my last Christmas show. It originaly aired both in the feed for The Unkle Bonehead Show and on UBSN.net. My first radio station that was all me. In it you will here me reference. Linux for the rest of us training videos. They are still available but pretty dated since this was recorded 2011-12-24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP-Ep20 Changing My Mind, Again!</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 05:29:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep20/</guid>
      <description>Download MP3 file
Preroll I&amp;rsquo;m tring something new, Pixelfed is in the news and a whole lot more coming up in number 20 of The Self Hosted Podcast!
Housekeeping and Support Support Framasoft- They are looking to bring live streaming to PeerTube!
Tool Tip VSCodium
News Fediverse Pixelfed awarded grant from NLnet
Russian Police Raid NGINX
Zepplin Ransomware targets Tech and Health Co
Snatch ransomware reboots windows in safe mode to bypass antivirus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP Ep19 Funkwhale - Putting the Pod back into Podcasting</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 07:10:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep19/</guid>
      <description>Download Here
Music provided by Unfa
Internet Archive could use your support! &amp;gt;I ask only once a year: please help the Internet Archive today. Right now, we have a 2-to-1 Matching Gift Campaign, so you can triple your impact! Most can’t afford to give, but we hope you can. The average donation is $45. If everyone reading this chips in just $5, we can end this fundraiser today. All we need is the price of a paperback book to sustain a non-profit website the whole world depends on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep18 LollipopCloud and Funkwhale Podcasters Group</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 20:52:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep18/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
Email me at unklebonehead@nixnet.email **This episode is brought to you by LollipopCloud
Housekeeping  @Naschbarschaft on Mastodon alerted me to mp3 enclosures were not in the rss feed for Bonehead Media.com Thank you I am learning how to put them into the rss templates in hugo. I will get this fixed.
 I didnt get to go home again so I&amp;rsquo;m in the truck again recording this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP-Ep-17 Epic News</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 19:02:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep17/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
This episode is brought to you by NixNet where freedom is served with a slice of liberty.
Pre Roll Recording on the run, a whole bunch of super exciting news in the Fediverse and a whole lot more coming up on episode 17 of The Self Hosted Podcast!
Banter  This episode will be out the week of November 17th. By the end of this week this podcast will have well over 1000 downloads on Anchor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep16 LimeSurvey and being dealt a shitty day</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 13:04:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep16/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
Big update since the recording! new contact email is unklebonehead@nixnet.email
News Massive exodus of India&amp;rsquo;s Twitter moved to Mastodon - This is a bull shit quote from the article. &amp;gt;While many have hailed Mastodon as a great alternative to Twitter, some have pointed out that its not as easy to use, which means its unlikely that Mastodon is going to take over - even in the long term.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP-Ep15 This is some scary s**t</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 06:38:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep15/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
News Links Yunohost 3.7 Testing asking for feedback
 We just released a new testing version for YunoHost and would be happy to receive feedback before releasing it as a stable version :yum:
This release includes quite important changes in YunoHost’s internal, and therefore requires careful validation to minimize the amount of remaining bugs.
 Major changes are: - Group and permission mechanism
 Improvements to detect app installs that broke critical parts of the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep14 Pubcast, WriteFreely and Plume</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 14:19:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep14/</guid>
      <description>Download Here
Music provided by Unfa
Follow me across the fediverse! unklebonehead@hzhome.ntroradio.com
So I got started on FreeCodeCamp As I mentioned in a blog post last week I want to learn how to code. Mainly so I can understand the topics I am covering here on this podcast and to help me be a better self hoster but I would love to get a new job where I am home a lot more than just 34 hrs a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSHP Ep13</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 07:14:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/tshp-ep13/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
PreRoll Advert - This episode is brought to you by The Fediverse. The Fediverse is a collection of nearly 40 decentralized apps that can connect with each other. You can join or even host an instance yourself on your own server. More than just social networks they cover just about everything from blogging to cloud storage. PeerTube, Plume, FunkWhale Visit Fediverse Party to learn more today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep12 Hubzilla and More News</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep12-hubzilla-and-more-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 04:44:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep12-hubzilla-and-more-news/</guid>
      <description>Download untracked Mp3 here
There is a video that I recorded for this to show Hubzilla. I will post it tomarrow in it&amp;rsquo;s own post.
Preroll Quick bit of news and then we play with Hubzilla. Right here on episode 12 of The Self Hosted Podcast!
Housekeeping Yunohost has been upgraded to 3.6.5.2 along with Yunohost Admin panel. It is now at 3.6.5. Nextcloud-ynh has also been updated to 15.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep11 News and Updates</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep11-news-and-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/ep11-news-and-updates/</guid>
      <description>Download untracked Mp3 here
I&amp;rsquo;m back! Now with a redneck, tricked out Frankenputer latop. But its powered by KDENeon and backedup by Yunohost. It&amp;rsquo;s episode 11 and I got some news, opinions and updates for you right here, right now on The Self Hosted Podcast.
Housekeeping My laptop broke. Thats why I&amp;rsquo;ve been silent. But I was able to jerry rig it enough that its usable. I&amp;rsquo;ll post pics or you can go see them on Mastodon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep10 Communication on Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-08-ep10-communitcation-on-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-08-ep10-communitcation-on-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
Pre-roll The last couple of weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve seen on these message signs over the highways the phrase &amp;ldquo;Turn signals-the original instant message&amp;rdquo;. And the talk on the CB radio was hilarious as you can imagine. But the one thing all of us truck drivers agree on is that the turn signal is not the original instant messsage. It&amp;rsquo;s the middle finger. And speaking of instant messenges this is Ep10:Communication on Yunohost right here, right now on The Self Hosted Podcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep9Getting Help with Your Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-01-ep9-getting-help-with-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-01-ep9-getting-help-with-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Ep 9  Download Mp3 Download two songs from me for free! CC4.0! Play them in your podcast if you have one! Hammer On Down Work It Out
Pre Roll I was at a TA truckstop earlier this week. And they had a Verizon kiosk inside and there was actually a Verizon employee there. I may have jokingly asked him if he had any phones that didnt have ios or android on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep8 Commit2Quit</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-25-ep8-commit2quit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-25-ep8-commit2quit/</guid>
      <description>Ep8 Commit2Quit  Download Here
Housekeeping It seems that this podcasts goal has already been achieved. It has inspired 2 people to start self hosting. I got a couple of notifications on Mastodon that one is researching on how to self host on bsd and the other actually installed Yunohost! Thats frickin AWESOME! CONGRATS TO BOTH OF YOU! And I sincerely hope it works out for each your situations. Especially the one doing it on bsd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep7 Securering Your Yunohost Server</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-18-ep7-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-18-ep7-security/</guid>
      <description>Ep7 Security  Download Mp3
Housekeeping I just recorded episode 4 of The Self Hosted Vidcast. I uninstalled Wordpress and showed how to install a static html site on Yunohost. Bonehead Media is back to being a simple static html site. It&amp;rsquo;s only got 2 pages that I built in Bootstrap Studio. I&amp;rsquo;ll flesh it out more in the future. I would like to turn it into a theme for Pelican or Hugo and post the shownotes to the front page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep6 How to Take Back Control</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-12-ep6-how/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-12-ep6-how/</guid>
      <description>Ep6 How to take back control  Download Here
How to take back control https://switching.social/guide-to-switching/
First we need to look at what we need to replace to rid our lives of these companies. 1. Communication/Email/Chat/Conferancing 2. Office/Doc/Colaboration 3. File storage/Sharing 4. News 5. Social Networking 6. Education 7. Entertainment
To truly get rid of Google you will need to replace your Android phone! More on this towards the end. These can all be covered using some ethical and free companies such as Framasoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep5 Getting Back Control</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-11-ep5-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-11-ep5-control/</guid>
      <description>Ep5 Getting Back Control  Download Here
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be totally honest with you. I didnt really think the course of this podcast through before starting it. I got excited when I found out about Yunohost and went totally ADD thinking that people have to know about this distro! I just hit record and started talking without thinking. I didnt put any kind of structure into it or really any kind of planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep4 The Internet Cube</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-04-ep4-the-internet-cube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-04-ep4-the-internet-cube/</guid>
      <description>Ep4 The Internet Cube  Download Mp3 #### Rethinking the direction of the podcast I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing some major thinking about the direction of where I want to take this podcast. I was listening to one of the episodes as I usually do. Us podcasters do that alot. Listen to ourselves in order to critique our abililites. We&amp;rsquo;re not really that self important, we are are our worst and toughest critics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep3 Why You Should Know DNS</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep3-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep3-dns/</guid>
      <description>Ep3 Why You Should Know DNS  Download Mp3 I love the artwork for this episode! And I just had to use it when I saw it. It was created by @aleks@cybre.space. I&amp;rsquo;ve also ran across a couple of memes that I cant stop laughing at. I&amp;rsquo;ll be using those in future episodes as well. The cat is out of the bag and people are discovering the podcast. So if you are new, well I guess at this point everybody is new, lol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep2 Choosing Yunohost and The Fediverse</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep2-choosing-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep2-choosing-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Ep2 Choosing Yunohost and The Fediverse 
Download Episode #### What it is If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever messed with Linux you have undoubtedly experienced the dreaded (but fun) thing called &amp;ldquo;distro hopping&amp;rdquo;. Where you constantly download and install tons of different distros and use them to see what they are like and how well they run. Hell you may be running 3-4 of them on a pc at any given time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep1 Six Questions</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep1-six-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep1-six-questions/</guid>
      <description>Ep1 Six Questions 
Download Mp3 Who, what, where, when, why and how.
Who am I? Greetings! If this is the first time you&amp;rsquo;ve ever ran across me I am Unkle Bonehead and welcome to the Self Hosted Podcast, a journey into taking control of your data and entering the Fediverse. It&amp;rsquo;s not only my journey but it just might be yours as well.
Why? Because large corporations such as Google, Facebook, Twitter, Amazon, etc have your data in their control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now With Less Google</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/now-with-less-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 07:45:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/truckinnutz/now-with-less-google/</guid>
      <description>Hopefully by the end of the week I will be 100% Google free. The only exception is on my phone. I am no longer using gmail except for a couple of login that I need to change and am working on porting all my emails over to my new email. Im also switching to the News app on Nextcloud for my rss reader and am deciding on whether or not I want to use Nextclouds Music app for my music library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>