<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Hosting on Bonehead Media</title>
    <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/tags/self-hosting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self Hosting on Bonehead Media</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyleft © 2019, All original content on this site is Creative Commons 4.0 Non Commercial-Share alike.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://boneheadmedia.com/tags/self-hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep10 Communication on Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-08-ep10-communitcation-on-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-08-ep10-communitcation-on-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Download Mp3
Pre-roll The last couple of weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve seen on these message signs over the highways the phrase &amp;ldquo;Turn signals-the original instant message&amp;rdquo;. And the talk on the CB radio was hilarious as you can imagine. But the one thing all of us truck drivers agree on is that the turn signal is not the original instant messsage. It&amp;rsquo;s the middle finger. And speaking of instant messenges this is Ep10:Communication on Yunohost right here, right now on The Self Hosted Podcast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep9Getting Help with Your Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-01-ep9-getting-help-with-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-09-01-ep9-getting-help-with-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Ep 9  Download Mp3 Download two songs from me for free! CC4.0! Play them in your podcast if you have one! Hammer On Down Work It Out
Pre Roll I was at a TA truckstop earlier this week. And they had a Verizon kiosk inside and there was actually a Verizon employee there. I may have jokingly asked him if he had any phones that didnt have ios or android on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I record my Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep5/</guid>
      <description>To be honest, this should be a &amp;ldquo;Dont drink and vidcast&amp;rdquo; video. I may or may not have had a couple of beers before recording this. This how I record all of my podcasts, whether I&amp;rsquo;m at home in the studio or on the road in the truck. The process and apps are all the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I am currently using on my Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep6/</guid>
      <description>Just me showing you what I am currently using on my own home server. Airsonic Grav Flat File CMS Searx Roundcube Nextcloud PeerTube TTRss</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep8 Commit2Quit</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-25-ep8-commit2quit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-25-ep8-commit2quit/</guid>
      <description>Ep8 Commit2Quit  Download Here
Housekeeping It seems that this podcasts goal has already been achieved. It has inspired 2 people to start self hosting. I got a couple of notifications on Mastodon that one is researching on how to self host on bsd and the other actually installed Yunohost! Thats frickin AWESOME! CONGRATS TO BOTH OF YOU! And I sincerely hope it works out for each your situations. Especially the one doing it on bsd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep7 Securering Your Yunohost Server</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-18-ep7-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-18-ep7-security/</guid>
      <description>Ep7 Security  Download Mp3
Housekeeping I just recorded episode 4 of The Self Hosted Vidcast. I uninstalled Wordpress and showed how to install a static html site on Yunohost. Bonehead Media is back to being a simple static html site. It&amp;rsquo;s only got 2 pages that I built in Bootstrap Studio. I&amp;rsquo;ll flesh it out more in the future. I would like to turn it into a theme for Pelican or Hugo and post the shownotes to the front page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to remove Wordpress from Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep4/</guid>
      <description>This is how you uninstall Wordpress and install a static html site to Yunohost. Get Yunohost - https://yunohost.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep6 How to Take Back Control</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-12-ep6-how/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-12-ep6-how/</guid>
      <description>Ep6 How to take back control  Download Here
How to take back control https://switching.social/guide-to-switching/
First we need to look at what we need to replace to rid our lives of these companies. 1. Communication/Email/Chat/Conferancing 2. Office/Doc/Colaboration 3. File storage/Sharing 4. News 5. Social Networking 6. Education 7. Entertainment
To truly get rid of Google you will need to replace your Android phone! More on this towards the end. These can all be covered using some ethical and free companies such as Framasoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep5 Getting Back Control</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-11-ep5-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-11-ep5-control/</guid>
      <description>Ep5 Getting Back Control  Download Here
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be totally honest with you. I didnt really think the course of this podcast through before starting it. I got excited when I found out about Yunohost and went totally ADD thinking that people have to know about this distro! I just hit record and started talking without thinking. I didnt put any kind of structure into it or really any kind of planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Wordpress on Yunohst</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep3/</guid>
      <description>Look how easy it is to install Wordpress on Yunohost! It only actually took minutes and minimal attention from me. But because I cant never shut up it made a 30 minute video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep4 The Internet Cube</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-04-ep4-the-internet-cube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshp/2019-08-04-ep4-the-internet-cube/</guid>
      <description>Ep4 The Internet Cube  Download Mp3 #### Rethinking the direction of the podcast I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing some major thinking about the direction of where I want to take this podcast. I was listening to one of the episodes as I usually do. Us podcasters do that alot. Listen to ourselves in order to critique our abililites. We&amp;rsquo;re not really that self important, we are are our worst and toughest critics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep3 Why You Should Know DNS</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep3-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep3-dns/</guid>
      <description>Ep3 Why You Should Know DNS  Download Mp3 I love the artwork for this episode! And I just had to use it when I saw it. It was created by @aleks@cybre.space. I&amp;rsquo;ve also ran across a couple of memes that I cant stop laughing at. I&amp;rsquo;ll be using those in future episodes as well. The cat is out of the bag and people are discovering the podcast. So if you are new, well I guess at this point everybody is new, lol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep2 Choosing Yunohost and The Fediverse</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep2-choosing-yunohost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep2-choosing-yunohost/</guid>
      <description>Ep2 Choosing Yunohost and The Fediverse 
Download Episode #### What it is If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever messed with Linux you have undoubtedly experienced the dreaded (but fun) thing called &amp;ldquo;distro hopping&amp;rdquo;. Where you constantly download and install tons of different distros and use them to see what they are like and how well they run. Hell you may be running 3-4 of them on a pc at any given time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ep1 Six Questions</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep1-six-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/posts/ep1-six-questions/</guid>
      <description>Ep1 Six Questions 
Download Mp3 Who, what, where, when, why and how.
Who am I? Greetings! If this is the first time you&amp;rsquo;ve ever ran across me I am Unkle Bonehead and welcome to the Self Hosted Podcast, a journey into taking control of your data and entering the Fediverse. It&amp;rsquo;s not only my journey but it just might be yours as well.
Why? Because large corporations such as Google, Facebook, Twitter, Amazon, etc have your data in their control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yunohst Post Intall</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep2/</guid>
      <description>The step called &amp;ldquo;post-installation&amp;rdquo; is actually the initial configuration of YunoHost. It has to be done just after the installation of the system itself. You can do it from through ssh, directly on the server or through a web browser. The browser is what I did because it is the easiest for people like me. Who dont know what they are doing.
Post-Installation The step called &amp;ldquo;post-installation&amp;rdquo; is actually the initial configuration of YunoHost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Yunohost</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/tshv/tshvep1/</guid>
      <description>Talking about and installing Yunohost. I used virtualbox instead of an actual machine but the process is the same. Step1 - Make coffee Step2 - Download the correct iso for your machine Step3 - Install</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>