<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Bonehead Media</title>
    <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Bonehead Media</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyleft © 2019, All original content on this site is Creative Commons 4.0 Non Commercial-Share alike.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 11:06:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://boneheadmedia.com/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ipfs Enabled</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/ipfs-enabled/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 11:06:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/ipfs-enabled/</guid>
      <description>In episode 21 of The Self Hosted Podcast I talked about IPFS. Well if you are reading this then I did it. This website is now on IPFS and you if I did it right it looks no different than the regular website. Which I hope I got it right because that would be so cool. But I still dont like that whatever you put on IPFS it&amp;rsquo;s online forever. So you better be sure you stand behind what you say and dont change your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I start another podcast?</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/considering-a-new-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 07:30:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/considering-a-new-podcast/</guid>
      <description>I have to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m actually considering it You may have figured out by now that when I find something new the first thing I do is look for a podcast about it. I know I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one in the world that does this. But this time I&amp;rsquo;m not so sure about starting it. I want to do it but I dont want to, lol. I&amp;rsquo;m so indecisive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking the Plunge on Full</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/taking-the-plunge-on-full/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 14:14:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/taking-the-plunge-on-full/</guid>
      <description>Hubzilla hour 36 update Well it&amp;rsquo;s been just over 36 hrs I&amp;rsquo;ve been on Hubzilla and I really do still like it. Wait, I love it! I like it so much that I am considering take the full on plunge and going in up to my neck in it. I want to get into exeriencing the full effect with the webpages app and build a site out of it. Just to see what I can do with my measley coding skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Updates</title>
      <link>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 21:11:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://boneheadmedia.com/post/blog/some-updates/</guid>
      <description>In case you hadn&amp;rsquo;t noticed I&amp;rsquo;ve been a bit busy here recently. Not only has the entire site been redone but it&amp;rsquo;s still not complete. While it is complete enough to get going with new content. Here is what I&amp;rsquo;ve done. - Now made with Hugo! I went back to Hugo because I like the simplicity of it and how I can make changes right on my laptop during the week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>